<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>English on 醉后的星星</title><link>http://kizx.gitee.io/tags/english/</link><description>Recent content in English on 醉后的星星</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-cn</language><copyright>kizx</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 14:50:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kizx.gitee.io/tags/english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>We live in an “age of anxiety”</title><link>http://kizx.gitee.io/post/we-live-in-an-age-of-anxiety/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kizx.gitee.io/post/we-live-in-an-age-of-anxiety/</guid><description>&lt;p>The teacher of our group introduced us to some research and views about anxiety. Although we are no longer suffering from diseases, hunger and war in the present era, we still need to worry about health, billing, study, work, interpersonal relationships and so on. We are not only anxious for the present, but also for the future.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After the speech, the teacher asked us three questions.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The first question is &amp;ldquo;Have you ever experienced mental anxiety, and what are you anxious about?&amp;rdquo;. Some of our team members are anxious about the exam, while others are worried about their relationship with their classmates, and generally we are all anxious about future work.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The second question is &amp;ldquo;What do you think are the causes of anxiety?&amp;rdquo;. After our group discussion, we have summarized the following reasons. First of all, we feel anxious because of the lack of knowledge of anxiety and lack of ability and experience. The second reason is our mentality. When we encounter challenging things, an optimistic and confident attitude will help us overcome anxiety. On the contrary, a negative attitude will contribute to our anxiety.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The last question is &amp;ldquo;Do you know how to relieve anxiety? Can you recommend some good ways to relieve anxiety?&amp;rdquo;. In response to the anxiety factors we discussed above, our group members believe that to relieve anxiety, we should first learn more and improve our abilities and experience. So that we can have enough confidence and optimism to overcome anxiety. If we are already in anxiety, we can use the means of self-motivation to distract ourselves from anxiety. And we think that proper venting or relaxation is also a good way to relieve anxiety.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Finally, I hope everyone can stay away from anxiety and enjoy life!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>IG Nobel Prize</title><link>http://kizx.gitee.io/post/ig-nobel-prize/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 17:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://kizx.gitee.io/post/ig-nobel-prize/</guid><description>&lt;p>Good afternoon everyone, then I will share with you a news about the IG Nobel Prize. This prize is an interesting imitation of the Nobel Prize, and it is awarded to those scientific achievements that first make people laugh, then make them think deeply.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This month, the 29th first Ig Nobel Prize was announced, and this year&amp;rsquo;s winners, covering 10 categories. So next I will choose some of them to introduce to you.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>First of all. The Medical Prize was awarded to Italian scientists for pizza and illness studies. The researchers showed that “often eat pizza ” seems to have a lower risk of cancer and heart attack. But there&amp;rsquo;s just one catch – the pizza must be made and eaten in Italy. Maybe they only did experiments on Italians.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The next prize is very interesting. The award for the Medical Education Prize is to train the surgeon with &amp;ldquo;clicker training&amp;rdquo;. People often use it to train dogs and other animals. But the study found that training a surgeon would be as similar as training a dog.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Biology Prize is more interesting. The researchers placed a group of live cockroaches and dead cockroaches in a strong magnetic field. After 20 minutes, the dead cockroaches could be sucked into the refrigerator like a sticker, but the live group could not. This research may reveal the connection between biology and magnetic fields, and could help in the development of new magnetic sensors.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Engineering Prize was awarded to the invention of an automatic baby-diaper-changing machine. That&amp;rsquo;s sounds like a good invention. unfortunately the machine doesn&amp;rsquo;t actually change the child&amp;rsquo;s diaper. Instead, it is a bit like an oven to dry the diaper.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Chemistry Prize examines how much saliva a 5-year-old child will produce one day. It turned out that the five-year-old child produce about 500 milliliter of saliva a day. But we are still not sure what the significance of this study.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The most funny award is the Physics Prize. Researchers had discovered how the wombat manages to produce cube-shaped poo. It&amp;rsquo;s the only animal in the world known to do this, and the team found the secret of the cube-shaped poo is their intestine movement. But the researchers still don&amp;rsquo;t know for sure why wombats evolved to produce cube-shaped poo.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>(Next is the Peace Prize. Tickling will always make you feel good. However, do you know which part of the body can effectively relieve itching? Do you know how to scratch to maximize your body and mind? This research will make you feel comfortable and scratched.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Economics Prize examines which country&amp;rsquo;s banknotes are the most susceptible to dangerous bacteria. Does this have anything to do with the economy?)&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>reference
&lt;a class="link" href="https://newatlas.com/science/ig-nobel-awards-2019/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>https://newatlas.com/science/ig-nobel-awards-2019/&lt;/a>
&lt;a class="link" href="https://mp.weixin.qq.com/s/jcjwCNhju1eK_ehSKHiq7g" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>https://mp.weixin.qq.com/s/jcjwCNhju1eK_ehSKHiq7g&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Questions&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Do you think the Ig Nobel Prize makes sense, or is it just for fun?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Which Prize do you think is the most interesting？&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Can you also give a similar interesting research?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol></description></item></channel></rss>